Why aren't they back yet?
Don't tell me...
They got lost?
Their phones are off too.
I'm starving to death.
Who knows, maybe they went on a date.
A date? (Support Admin Watch on
kissasia.cam or kisskh.org)
They're back.
Isn't that Secretary Lin?
This...
Back so early?
President Qin.
Have a seat.
Well, President Qin...
Let's start eating then.
Everyone's hungry.
Let's eat.
The hotpot here...
Is absolutely top-notch.
We order it every time we come.
Every single time.
To celebrate President Qin...
Attending for the first time...
Our Secretarial Department's team building.
I propose we all...
Have a drink together.
Great!
Come on, come on.
Cheers, cheers!
Boss.
To protect your image...
Please drink in moderation.
Don't worry.
I know my limits.
Come on, let's toast.
Thanks for your hard work.
Titi.
Let me ask you...
Are you...
In love with our Secretary Lin?
Yes.
But you always hog him.
You don't even share the broth with us.
What can I do?
It's because Secretary Lin...
Doesn't like you.
Doesn't like me?
Then does he like you?
Of course he does.
At this table...
Is there anyone who doesn't like me?
We like you.
No, no.
Probably not, right?
Penalty drink!
What's the matter, boss?
I'm sorry.
Because we reserve rooms...
Based on your headcount each visit.
We reserve rooms.
This time, for some reason...
You have an extra person.
So...
There are no extra rooms, is that it?
I'm very sorry.
It's fine.
Don't worry about it.
Okay.
Come on, come on.
Let's have a toast.
Cheers!
Let's toast.
Take it easy.
I'm fine.
Secretary Lin.
I wore these high heels for you.
She's had too much to drink.
Secretary Lin.
I'll take Titi back.
She drank too much today.
Don't take what she said to heart.
Take good care of our President Qin.
Bye-bye.
I'm not drunk.
What is it?
Han.
I miss you.
If there's nothing else, I'm hanging up.
Don't.
Don't be so cruel.
I...
You're still the same as before.
Lin Han.
It was very hard for me alone abroad.
I happened to meet someone...
Who could understand me.
So I felt a bit grateful.
Maybe I hadn't experienced enough.
And thought that was love.
I'm not interested...
In any of your affairs.
But we've been together since university.
We've always been a good match.
Do you remember that...
I'm not interested in the past either.
I'm leaving first.
Lin Han!
For the sake of me being alone...
And having come such a long way...
Accept me, okay?
I really miss you.
At least for now...
Don't make me leave.
I'm all alone...
It's really dangerous.
This way, please.
Mm, okay.
This young lady is really lucky.
This is a room...
A guest has booked long-term.
I just called and asked.
She's not staying here tonight.
So you can stay here for now.
Okay.
Then you stay here for now.
Leave when it's light out.
Lin Han.
Give me another chance.
Let's start over.
Okay?
You really never understood me.
Sorry.
I thought you were staying here.
I just went to get gas.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
In the future, learn from Secretary Lin...
How to manage your time.
Ah, okay.
By the way...
Isn't Secretary Lin with you?
Secretary Lin?
Oh, yes.
That's right.
President Qin is in the car.
Alright, alright, don't worry.
Okay.
Time Assassin
Lao Wang
From now on, you can call him Lin Ike.
Why did you leave early?
Why do you care about my business?
Did I do something
to make you angry?
Yes. Very angry.
What can I do to make you not angry anymore?
Does Secretary Lin talk to everyone like this?
What?
Player.
Indiscriminately caring for every woman.
Are you the Ambassador of Tenderness, may I ask?
You're jealous.
No.
Let's be together, Meili.
What?
If this will make you stop being angry,
Someone who once gave their heart freely was betrayed.
It always seems to take a long time
to accept it calmly.
But I don't know when it started,
maybe the first time I saw her
do that kind of thing for me.
Or maybe, even earlier.
My heart was slowly occupied by her,
until it was completely full.
Only today did I realize
that I
am very afraid of losing her.
I want to be with her.
Once that thought sprouts,
it can never be diminished.
Let's be together, Meili.
My Big Sis.
Just like our first pinky promise.
Who on earth gave him the courage?
Lao Wang.
Who do you think it was?
Are you talking about Secretary Lin?
Oh, right.
When I was checking you out just now,
the landlady said rooms were scarce,
so she specially freed up a room for him.
But he gave it to a girl.
Out here in the deep mountains,
staying outside for a night
does require some courage.
What did you say?
You...
You didn't know?
Turn the car around.